let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What brand is known as the Golden Arches?",
    answer: "McDonalds",
    options: ["McDonalds", "Carl's JR", "Taco Bell", "Wendys"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In beer, what does IPA stand for?",
    answer: "Indian Pale Ale",
    options: [
      "International Phonetic Aplphabet",
      "Ingrediants Per Alchohol",
      "Indian Pale Ale",
      "International Phonetic Association",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "What is the main non-alcoholic ingredient of a White Russian cocktail?",
    answer: "Milk",
    options: ["Creme", "Milk", "Coffee", "Orange Juice"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The Chinese Gooseberry is also known as a what?",
    answer: "Kiwi Fruit",
    options: ["Orange", "Kiwi Fruit", "Banana", "Lime"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Vindaloo, Madras and Korma are all famous dishes of which tyoe of cuisine?",
    answer: "Indian Curry",
    options: ["Indian Curry", "Mexican", "Chinese", "American"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Vanilla is native of which country?",
    answer: "Madagascar",
    options: ["Africa", "Europe", "Spain", "Madagascar"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "What coloured vegetable is now mainly orange but can also be purple and yellow?",
    answer: "Carrots",
    options: ["Beets", "Califlour", "Carrots", "Tomato"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What brand has the slogan 'Have a break, have a 'what''?",
    answer: "Kit Kat",
    options: ["Snickers", "Milkyway", "Rolo", "Kit Kat"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The Whopper is made by which fast food company?",
    answer: "Burger King",
    options: ["Burger King", "McDonalds", "Taco Time", "Arbys"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the main ingredent of bread?",
    answer: "Flour",
    options: ["Eggs", "Milk", "Yeast", "Flour"],
  },
];
